

## Dani Zelezniak

+++

Dani Zelezniak is an experienced CEO, angel investor and entrepreneur with expertise in technology, marketplace platforms, and mobile apps. He co-founded kVisi, Israel's largest ondemand laundry and drycleaning app, and WeCast, a platform connecting talent with entertainment industry and global ad opportunities, including at HBO, Netflix and Sony. Dani serves as chairman of Kviscal services LTD the largest industrial laundry equipment company in Israel. Dani also has experience in real-estate development. Dani's hobbies are professional boxing, his pets, reading books, meditating and spending time with his friends and

Fun fact about Dani: Dani loves to take ice-baths.

### **CONTACT**

dzelezniak29@gmail.com

### **EDUCATION**

Ono Academic College
Bachelor of Laws - LLB,
Law2015 – 2019

**Tel Aviv University**Directors course 2014

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**



### **Co-Founder and Co-Chief Executive Officer**

kVisi - Jun 2018 - Present (4 yrs)

- Head of Israel's largest app-based, on-demand laundry and dry cleaning delivery service.
- Servicing more than 10% of clients living in the Tel Aviv metro, Ramat Gan, Givatayim, Hertzliya, Petah Tikva, Kiryat Ono, Ra'anana and Ramat Ha'Sharon with year-over-year growth and penetration of 3x while handling dozens of tons of laundry per month.
- algorithm that ensures narrow delivery window times are met and tracks client clothing location in real-time.



# Co-Founder, Angel Investor

**WECAST Inc. -** Jul 2016 – June 2020

- Co-founded WeCast, an online marketplace with active management that lets models, actors and aspiring talent land prestigious jobs across the entertainment industry, without the need for an agent.
- Created over \$2M in job opportunities in 2019 (828% YoY growth from 2018), and grew to +24K users in 18 months.
- Secured major ad agency partners including Ogilvy, M&C SAATCHI, 99Cents, and TBWA.
- Have been featured in ads for global brands such as Airbnb, Gucci, Adidas, VW, Mercedes, Rolls-Royce, AMEX, Burger King, Coca Cola, Samsung, among others.



### Contributor

Forbs - Jan 2021 - Present



# **Board Member; Co-Chief Executive Officer**

Kviscal services Co. LTD. - Aug 2011 - Present (11 yrs)

 Co-CEO of Israel's largest rental company of sustainable industrial laundry equipment and detergents, servicing hotels, hospitals, senior citizen living facilities, self-operated laundry companies, as well as providing services to clients across all of Israel, renting thousands of sustainable laundry machines.



#### Director

Galdani LTD. - Mar 2007 - Jun 2010 (3 yrs)

 Created one of Israel's first short-term, custom outfitted work spaces.